(Sheldon:)But the flash drive
is in a locked drawer in my desk.
(Summer:)- So?
- The key is hidden in my room.
- Penny'd have to go into my room.
(Summer:)- So?
- People don't go in my room.
(Leonard:)I see. Well, it seems once again...
(Leonard:)...you're caught
between a rock and a crazy place.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I hate when that happens.
(Howard(steeling himself to talk to Summer Glau, to himself):)It's hot in here. Must be Summer.
It's hot in here. Must be summer.
- That's cute.
- Really? I just made it up.
(Raj:)Have you seen Slumdog Millionaire?
(Summer:)Oh yeah, I loved it.
(Raj:)It's loosely based on my life.
(Penny:)We're putting the play on for one night
in this little 99-seat theater.
(Penny:)Can you come? Oh, great.
(Penny:)Do you know 98 other people
that might wanna come?
Oh, hang on. Hello?
Listen. I'm about to give you
a set of instructions...
(Sheldon(on phone):)...which you must follow to the letter.